[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Sheldon:)What fresh hell is this?
- Hey, Penny. Come on in.
- Hey, guys.
(Howard:)See a Penny, pick her up,
and all the day, you'll have good luck.
(Penny:)No, you won't. Uh...
- Can I hide out here for a while?
- Sure. What's going on?
(Penny:)Well, there's this girl I know
from back in Nebraska, Christy.
(Penny:)She called me up,
she's like, "Hey, how's California?"
And I'm like, "Awesome,"
because it's not Nebraska.
(Penny:)The next thing I know,
she's invited herself to stay with me.
- Eight oh eight.
- Shh.
(Penny:)She got here today
and she's just been in my apartment...
...yakking about every guy she slept with
in Omaha, which is every guy in Omaha...
(Penny:)...and washing
the sluttiest collection of underwear...
(Penny:)...you have ever seen
in my bathroom sink.
(Howard:)Is she doing it one thong at a time
or does she throw it all in?
Like some sort of erotic bouillabaisse?
- He really needs to dial it down.
- I know.
So if you don't like this Christy,
why are you letting her stay?
(Penny:)She was engaged to my cousin
while sleeping with my brother...
(Penny:)...so she's kind of family.
Yeah, I apologize for my earlier outburst.
Who needs "Halo"
when we can be regaled...
(Sheldon:)...with the delightfully folksy tale
of the whore of Omaha?
(Leonard:)Oh... I don't think she's a whore.
(Penny:)No, yeah, she's definitely a whore.
(Penny:)I mean, she has absolutely no standards.
(Penny:)This one time, she was at...
(Penny:)Where's Howard?
HOWARD:
Bonjour, mademoiselle.
(Howard(voice off):)I understand you're new in town.
(Sheldon:)Oh, good grief.